What were some of the steps that you kind of learned to
take during that process to focus on your personal and mental health?
Well, I think the obvious answer that always people
go back to, and it really is true, is exercise.
But it's also the one thing we always tend to cut out
first because it seems to be the one fungible thing that we're like,
oh, you know, I'll do that tomorrow or I won't
do that because I've got this meeting today or so forth.
Anybody who's looking for a good entrepreneurial work-life
balance, I would encourage them to partner with somebody.
I think there's no way I could have ever built my
company if I hadn't have a strong co-partner in founding the company.
And we were able to offload a lot of things for each other,
whether it was somebody has a personal emergency or just dividing up the work.
And finding somebody you trust is critical.
And somebody you enjoy working with and also somebody
who has not just complementary but even non-complementary skills
so that you both bring something to
the table that the other one doesn't have.